他们告诉我了，但我不知道。
They told me, but I had no idea.
露露吗?
Lulu?
萝拉。
It's Lola.
谁在乎呢?我付钱让你坐下?
Well, who gives a shit? I'm paying you to sit down?
这里一个人也没有。
There's no one here.
你想当聪明人，起来吧。
Oh, you want to be a smart ass. Get up.
来吧，亲爱的。开始工作吧。时间就是金钱。
Come on, sweetheart. Get to work. Time's money.
回去把小牛薯条糊了。
Get back there and batter them calf fries.
你弄完之后，再包些银器。
When you're done with that, wrap some silverware.
有很多工作要做。
Plenty of work to do.
我得告诉你们这些该死的孩子。
Gotta tell you goddamn kids everything.
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck?
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
-搞定了吗?-不，还没做好。
- Is it done? - No, it's not done.
那家伙刚骑着马停了下来。
The guy just pulled up on a fucking horse.
——所以呢?-所以你不能杀死一个骑马的人!
- So? - So you can't kill a guy on a horse!
他还骑在马上吗?
Well, is he still on the horse?
没有，他刚进去了。
No, he just went inside the place.
太好了。问题解决了。
Great. Problem solved.
想想你的孩子，做你该做的，完事后给我打电话。
Think about your kid, do what you gotta do, and call me when it's done.
听着，多姆，等等。
Look, Dom, hold on.
不,Dom。喂?Dom ?
No, Dom. Hello? Dom?
他妈的!
Fuck!
嗯哼。
Ahem.
-第一天，亲爱的?-是的，先生。
- First day, darling? - Yes, sir.
-弗洛怎么了?-弗洛通过了。
- What happened to Flo? - Flo passed.
可怜的弗洛。
Poor Flo.
和我在一起十三年了。
Thirteen years been with me.
——露露……-还是萝拉。
- Lulu... - Still Lola.
给博格斯先生来杯咖啡，如果你不忙的话。
Coffee for Mr. Boggs, if you're not too busy.
快点说。
Make it quick.
好吧。
All right.
Okay.
我们走吧。我们走吧。
Let's go. Let's go.
谢谢你，女士。
Thank you, ma'am.
我可以用一下洗手间吗?
Would it be okay if I use the bathroom?
一条尾巴，是吧?
Some piece of tail, huh?
我觉得那女孩是黑寡妇的人。
I think that girl belongs to The Black Widow.
再说一遍好吗?
Come again?
去他的，去他的，去他的。
Fuck it, fuck it, fuck it, fuck it.
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
听着，我不想伤害你，沃尔特。
Look, I don't want to hurt you, Walter.
好吧?
Okay?
原谅我吗?
Excuse me?
你欠保利·罗素很多钱。
You owe Pauly Russo a lot of money.
你是?
And you are?
嗯,嗯…我的工作…我不为保利工作。
Uh, um... I work... Well, I don't work for Pauly.
我很了解多姆，他为保利工作。
I know Dom really well, and he works for Pauly.
你认识多姆吗?没关系。
Do you know Dom? It doesn't matter.
听着，我不想这么做。我真的不知道，好吗?
Look, I don't want to do this. I really don't, okay?
所以如果你能把欠保利的钱还给他…如果你能做到这一点，一切就都没事了没人会被杀或发生类似疯狂的事，好吗?
So if you could just pay Pauly the money that you owe him... If you could just do that, everything will be cool and no one has to get killed or anything crazy like that, okay?
咖啡吗?
Coffee?
他不会留下来的。
He's not staying.
好吧。
Okay.
你说呢，沃尔特?
What do you say, Walter?
遵命，遵命。
Yes, sir. Yes, sir.
哦,狗屎。哦,狗屎!
Oh, shit. Oh, shit!
嘿!你!
Hey! You!
那家伙死了吗?
Is that guy dead?
-要我查一下吗?-好的，谢谢。
- Would you like me to check? - Yes, please.
-看起来死定了。-哦，该死。
- Looks pretty dead. - Oh, shit.
怎么啦？什么狗屎?
What? What shit?
你得跟我来。我真的很抱歉，但你得跟我走。
You gotta come with me. I'm really sorry but you gotta come with me.
——什么?-你听到了。来吧，现在。走了。
- What? - You heard me. Come on, now. Go.
他妈的。来吧。
Fuck. Come on.
萝拉。
Lola.
你刚才跟我说什么?你刚才跟我说什么?
What'd you just say to me? What'd you just say to me?
-我的名字。-你叫什么名字?
- My name. - Your name?
把钥匙给我。他妈的在哪里…我拿到钥匙了。把你的手机给我。
Give me the keys. Where the fuck... I got the keys. Give me your phone.
——为什么?-因为我说了我有枪。
- Why? - Because I have a gun and I said so.
这就是为什么。把你的手机给我。现在。现在。现在。
That's why. Give me your fucking phone. Now. Now. Now.
你为什么这么做?
Why did you do that?
别再问我问题了。让你做什么就做什么。
Stop asking me questions. Do what you're told.
别动，好吗?留在原地。听到了吗?
Don't move, okay? Stay put. You hear me?
点头。留在原地。好吧?
Nod your head. Stay put. Okay?
这一点都不好笑。
It's not fucking funny.
拜托，来吧，来吧，来吧。
Please, come on, come on, come on.
-我们没事吧?-我搞砸了，多姆
- Are we good? - I fucked up, Dom.
上帝啊，杰姬。你做了什么?
Jesus Christ, Jackie. What did you do?
-他跑了。-这怎么可能?
- He got away. - How is that possible?
-你们没告诉我他有枪-这有什么区别?
- You guys didn't tell me that he'd have a gun. - What difference does it make?
这有什么区别?这算什么问题啊?
What difference does it make? What kind of a question is that?
枪会杀人，多姆。
Guns kill people, Dom.
看到了吗，杰姬?这个!
You see this, Jackie? This!
-这就是我不支持你的原因。-对不起。为我挺身而出?
- This is why I don't stand up for you. - I'm sorry. Stand up for me?
是的，你来找我，“我有个问题。我需要帮助。”
Yeah, you come to me, "I have a problem. I need help."
每一次都是彻头彻尾的灾难。
Every fucking time, it's an unmitigated disaster.
去你妈的。我什么时候向你要过东西?
Fuck you. When did I ever ask you for shit?
25年了，我才求你什么?
Twenty-five fucking years, I ask you for something?
是的,真的。你所做的。
Yes, actually. You did.
你所要做的就是在第二回合摔倒。
All you had to do is take a dive in the second round.
你会怎么做?
What do you do?
你他妈第二回合就把他打晕了!
You fucking knock the guy out in the second round!
好吧。好吧，好吧。那家伙是个流浪汉，好吗?
Okay. All right, all right. That guy was a bum, okay?
他是个流浪汉，我几乎没碰过他。
He was a bum, and I barely touched him.
那是很久以前的事了。
That was very long time ago.
杰姬，我受够你了。
Jackie, I'm done fucking with you.
告诉我发生了什么事。
Just tell me what happened.
-我想我杀了厨子。-谁?
- I think I killed the cook. - The who?
我可能在那个牛仔跑掉之前不小心跟他提了保利的名字。
I-I might have accidentally mentioned Pauly's name to the cowboy guy before he got away.
杰姬，你现在在哪?
Jackie, where are you right now?
你他妈的现在在哪儿?
Where are you right fucking now?
杰基?杰基?
Jackie? Jackie?
他妈的。
Fuck.
萝拉?
Lola?
他妈的!
Fuck!
他妈的。停!他妈的停止!
Fuck. Stop! Fucking stop!
我他妈不会还手的，住手!
I'm not gonna fucking hit you back, now stop!
-去你妈的!——停止。
- Fuck you! - Stop.
去你妈的!
Fuck you!
他妈的!停!
Fuck! Stop!
他妈的!画画。他妈的停止!
Fuck! Draw. Fucking stop!
——好吗?不用再跑了。——好。
- Okay? No more running. - Fine.
你能保证吗?
Do you promise?
你可能是体育史上最坏的罪犯。
You might be the worst criminal in the history of the sport.
-我不是罪犯。——很明显。
- I am not a criminal. - Clearly.
我不是。我对天发誓，这不是我。
I'm not. I swear to God, this isn't me.
我同意杀沃尔特是因为我孩子在坐牢。
I only agreed to kill that guy Walter because my kid's in jail.
我需要钱给他请律师。
I need the money to get him a lawyer.
你同意杀人就为了让你的孩子请律师?
You agreed to kill someone so that your kid could have a lawyer?
是的。
Yeah.
你傻吗?
Are you stupid?
欢迎来到丛林，混蛋们。
Welcome to the jungle, motherfuckers.
你不吃东西。你不睡觉。
You don't eat. You don't sleep.
没有我的允许你连屎都不能拉。
You can't even shit without my permission.
我他妈才不管你是不是眼睛冒出来脸变红了。
I don't give a fuck if your eyes pop out and your face turns red.
但你不用担心这个，对吗?巧克力滴?
But you don't have to worry about that, do you... chocolate drop?
你把可卡因卖给谁了?
Who'd you sell crack to?
你的妹妹吗?你的阿姨吗?你孩子的妈妈?
Your sister? Your aunt? Your baby mama?
我打赌你一定认为我们是一样的。
I bet you think you and me are the same.
你最好相信，我会打爆你的黑屁股就像我打爆你身边的白饼干一样快。
Best believe I'll bust your black ass just as quick as I'd bust that white bread cracker standing next to you.
你他妈到底是谁?
And who the fuck are you supposed to be?
你他妈的叫什么名字?
What's your fucking name?
比利的权力。
Billy Powers.
比利的力量……欢迎来到丛林，混蛋。
Billy Powers... Welcome to the jungle, motherfucker.
你他妈现在在跟我说什么?
What the fuck are you telling me right now?
-我不太确定，保利。-为什么?
- I'm not really sure, Pauly. - Why is that?
我想是因为我信息不足吧。
I guess because I'm short on information.
-你矮?-靠情报，是的。
- You're short? - On information, yeah.
我不希望你这样，多姆。
Well, I need you not to be, Dom.
我他妈都不能再说了。
I can't even fucking repeat that.
我会查清楚发生了什么事。
I'll find out what happened.
嗯，那很好。太他妈好了。
Well, that's good. That's really fucking good.
-是的。——这?
- Yeah. - This?
-不妙，多姆。-我知道。
- Not good, Dom. - I know that.
你他妈知道就好了。这很好。
Well, it's good you fucking know. That's good.
我希望你也知道这是你的责任。
I hope you also know that this is on you.
这都是你的错。
This is your fucking fault.
走了。去他妈的把它搞定。
Go. Go fucking take care of it.
你他妈的让我心烦意乱。
You give me fucking agita.
抱歉，那个厨师是你朋友吗?
Sorry, was that cook a friend of yours?
发生了什么事?
What happened?
如果你不介意，我们就不寒暄了。
If it's okay with you, maybe we can skip the pleasantries.
我被绑架了，我要走回车上。
I've been kidnapped, I'm walking back to the car.
我们就这样吧。
Let's just leave it at that.
你不需要举手。太好了。
You don't have to put your hands up. That's great.
-这显然是一个尴尬的局面。——是的。
- This is obviously an awkward situation. - Yes.
我想如果我对你略知一二，-就不必了好吧。-不会尴尬的。好吧。
Well, I figured maybe if I knew a thing or two about you, - it wouldn't have to be-- Right. - It won't be awkward. Okay.
我是萝拉。我已经说过了。
I'm Lola. I've said that already.
几年前我搬到哥斯达黎加开了一所表演学校，因为生活在这里让我想起了两件事……失败和创伤。还有别的事吗?
I moved to Costa Rica a few years ago to open an acting school because living here reminded me of two things... failure and trauma. Anything else?
你在哥斯达黎加开了一所表演学校?
You, uh-- You opened an acting school in Costa Rica?
-没有成功。-太令人震惊了。
- It didn't work out. - That's shocking.
我为这一切感到抱歉。
I'm sorry about all this.
好吧。
Okay.
你的车不是就在这里吗?
Wasn't your car right here?
妈的，我放弃。
Fuck, I give up.
去他妈的，伙计!只是他妈的…他妈的!
Just fuck it all, man! Just fucking... fuck!
你他妈在哭吗?
Are you fucking crying?
-我真的不是罪犯。-是的。
- I'm really not a criminal. - Yeah.
-我明白了。-我在为我儿子做正确的事。
- I'm getting that. - I'm trying to do right by my son.
这就是我要做的。
That's all I'm trying to do.
这个可怜的孩子根本没有机会。
This poor fucking kid never had a chance.
你觉得我是个混蛋?你应该见见他妈妈。
You think I'm an asshole? You should meet his mother.
如果你现在想跑，或者走，或者其他什么，我不会拿它来对付你，所以你可以去吧。
If you want to run now, or walk, or whatever, I'm not gonna hold it against you, so you can go ahead.
你就这么坐着吗?
Well, are you just gonna sit there?
不，我现在不是因为谋杀被通缉，就是…是啊，我会被那些雇我去杀我没杀的人的人杀了。
No, I'm either currently wanted for murder, or I'm... Yeah, I'm gonna be murdered by the guys who hired me to murder the guy I did not murder.
所以，是的，坐在这里似乎是明智之举。
So, yeah, sitting here seems-- seems like the move.
你有更好的主意吗?我接受任何建议。
You got any better ideas? I'll take any suggestions.
也许我能帮你。
Maybe I can help you.
-你在耍我吗?-不，我不会那么做。
- Are you fucking with me? - No, I wouldn't do that.
你是个拿着枪的大块头。
You're a big scary man with a gun.
还有，你肯定没子弹了。
Also, pretty sure you're out of bullets.
你为什么要帮我?
Why would you help me?
也许我们可以互相帮助。
Maybe we can help each other.
我他妈应该去检查一下我的脑袋，因为我又相信了这个白痴。
I should have my fucking head examined for trusting this idiot again.
-是我的错。-不不不不
- It's my fault. - No, no, no, no.
这是我的错。都是你十年前的错，你告诉我他会输掉比赛。
It's my fault. It was your fault 10 years ago, when you told me he'd throw the fucking fight.
是我的错，我听了第二次，好吗?
It's my fault for listening the second time, okay?
愚弄我一次，是你的耻辱。骗我两次…只是我们是一起长大的。
Fool me once, shame on you. Fool me twice... It's just that we grew up together.
他以前是个聪明的混蛋。
He used to be a smart fuck.
-我不知道发生了什么。-我刚说了是我的错
- I don't know what happened. - I just said it was my fault.
你想让我热起来吗?
You want to get me hot?
是啊，但你说听我的话是你的错，仔细想想也算是我的错了。
Yeah, but you said it was your fault for listening to me, which kind of makes it my fault if you think about it.
我他妈的不想去想。
I don't want to fucking think about it.
我就是这个意思，多姆，好吗?
That's what I'm saying, Dom, okay?
现在你想让我爽吗?
Now you want to get me fucking hot?
你是想让我欲火焚身，还是想放手?
You want to get me fucking hot, or you want to let it go?
——好。-谢谢，很好。谢谢你！
- Fine. - Thank you, that is fine. Thank you.
明天，第一件事，我要你去找那个该死的堕落牛仔看看你能不能把这事摆平，好吗?
Now tomorrow, first thing, I want you to go and see that fucking degenerate cowboy and see if you can straighten this fucking out, all right?
谁知道呢?也许这是最好的结果。
Who knows? Maybe it's all for the best.
-你做得对。——什么?
- You did the right thing. - What?
我是说，你做得对，把他砍了。
You did the right thing, I'm saying, having the guy clipped.
他六个星期欠你十万。你做得对。
He owed you 100 grand for six weeks. You did the right thing.
你现在是自作聪明吗?
Are you being a fucking wise ass right now?
-你在耍我吗，多姆?-什么意思?
- Are you fucking with me, Dom? - What do you mean?
我是什么意思?你什么意思，我他妈什么意思?
What do I mean? What do you mean, what the fuck do I mean?
这他妈不管用。但是没有成功。"我把他剪掉了"是什么意思?
It didn't fucking work. It didn't work. What do you mean, "I had him clipped"?
-我只是说说而已。-别说了。
- I'm just saying. - Don't say.
我他妈不想听你说，好吗?做的!
I don't want you to fucking say, all right? Do!
我他妈不想你说。
I don't want you to fucking say.
回想起来，我想要我的一百堆，如果你没意见的话。-我知道了。
In retrospect, I would like to have my hundred stacks, - if that's okay with you. - I got it.
好。现在，明天第一件事，你出去把这个牛仔的破事解决了。
Good. Now, tomorrow first thing, you go out there and you take care of this fucking thing with this cowboy.
希望能成功，然后我要你找到那个该死的杰基直接把他带来见我。
Hopefully, with some success, and then I want you to find that fucking cunt Jackie and I want you to bring him to me directly.
明白了吗?
Are we fucking clear?
-是的，是的。我们清楚。-是的，是的。
- Yeah, yeah. We're clear. - Yeah, yeah.
你他妈到底怎么回事?
What the fuck is going on with you?
-怎么了?-怎么了?
- What's happening? - What's happening?
你他妈在干什么?
What the fuck are you doing?
-你在干什么?-你为什么躲起来?
- What are you doing? - Why are you hiding?
没人知道我在那家餐厅工作。
No one knows that I work at that fucking diner.
-我他妈很谨慎-哦，小心点!
- I'm being fucking discreet. - Oh, discreet!
至于其他嫌疑人，一个已经死了据我们所知，可能是另一个杀了他?
And pertaining to the others of concern, one's dead and for all we know, the other might have killed him, okay?
——嘘!-放轻松。哦，别嘘我!
- Shh! - Just relax. Oh, don't shush me!
这是我的地盘，好吗?
This is my fucking neighborhood, okay?
我的天啊。我的天啊。我的天啊。
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
顺便说一句，说到你的邻居，你在那个破地方工作干什么?
By the way, speaking of your fucking neighborhood, what were you doing working at that shithole?
-你显然很有钱。-不不不。
- You're clearly rich. - No, no, no.
这是我妈妈的房子。她丰富的。
This is my mom's house. She's rich.
说实话，她的前夫都很有钱。
Truth be told, her ex-husbands are rich.
-她只是幸运而已。——嗯。
- She's just lucky. - Uh-huh.
不好意思，你说的是前夫吗?
I'm sorry, did you say ex-husbands with an "S"?
全部四个。有钱，死了。
All four of them. Rich and dead.
他们叫我妈妈"黑寡妇"
They call my mom "The Black Widow."
哦,太棒了。
Oh, great.
好吧……我们只有这些了，除非你想穿我的衣服。
Okay... This is all we got, unless you want to wear something of mine.
我的继父。
My stepdad's.
最后一个。
The last one.
好吧，事情是这样的。
Okay, here's the deal.
我们明天开着我妈的捷豹去医院。
We take my mom's Jag to the hospital tomorrow.
你和我是一对，我们打算结婚然后回哥斯达黎加。她买下了，我就给你一部分钱请你儿子的律师，
You and I are a couple, and we plan on getting married and going back to Costa Rica. She buys it, and I'll give you some of the money for your son's lawyer,
然后我就能回哥斯达黎加还房贷了
and I get to go back to Costa Rica and pay my mortgage.
你什么都不说还是你就一直这样点头?
You gonna say anything or are you just gonna keep nodding your head like that?
好吧，我们为什么要结婚?
Okay, why are we getting married?
因为…这是我母亲遗嘱的唯一条件。
Because... it's the sole condition of my mother's will.
-我不会杀你妈妈的-我很感激。
- I'm not killing your mother. - I appreciate that.
-搞什么鬼?-我不想你杀了我妈妈。
- Well, what the fuck? - I don't want you to kill my mom.
好吧。
Okay.
如果我们能让她相信我们要结婚了，我们的想法是，她会把我在她死后，但在她死前得到的一部分钱预付给我。
If we can lead her to believe that we are getting married, the idea would be that she would advance me some of the money that I'd be getting after she died, but before she dies.
-对不起，这太荒谬了。-不，杰基。
- I'm sorry, but that's ridiculous. - No, Jackie.
可笑的是你今早可能杀了人，然后绑架了我，或者你想绑架我，而我却给你一个藏身之所，一些衣服，还有赚钱的方法。
What's ridiculous is that you probably killed someone this morning, and then you kidnapped me, or you tried to, and here I am offering you a place to hide, some clothing, and a way to make money.
你有更好的主意吗，爱因斯坦?
You got any better ideas, Einstein?
好,看。我儿子的拘留听证会在三天后。
Okay, look. My son's detention hearing is in three days.
这一天基本上将决定他的余生如何度过。
That's a day that will basically determine how the rest of his life plays out.
我还没请到律师呢。
I don't even have the lawyer yet.
嗯?
Hmm?
我妈妈得癌症快死了。
My mom's dying of cancer.
我不想在这里跟你较劲，但有时候生活是艰难的。
I don't want to get in a pissing contest here, but sometimes life is tough.
我们现在在一起了。
We're in this together now.
那很好。
Well, that's nice.
分开。
Separately.
好吧，尽量休息一下。
All right, try to get some rest.
这可不容易。我妈妈是个禽兽。
This ain't gonna be easy. My mom's an animal.
-我睡在哪里?-有五间卧室。
- Where do I sleep? - There's, like, five bedrooms.
我不知道。选择一个。
I don't know. Choose one.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
-是啊，嘿。-我是缓刑部门的雷蒙德·钱德勒。
- Yeah, hey. -  This is Raymond Chandler, from the probation department.
我刚接到地方检察官的电话关于一个叫比利·鲍尔斯的孩子的案子，他和你们在那边等着审判，我想他是上周被处理的。
I just got a call from the D.A. 's office about a kid named Billy Powers, who's awaiting trial with you guys over there who was processed last week, I believe.
总之，很明显，这孩子有糖尿病，他来的时候没有列出来，所以你们帮我个大忙，如果你们能帮我照顾他。
Anyway, apparently, this kid's diabetic and, uh, it wasn't listed when he came in, so you guys would be doing me a big favor if you could look out for him.
也许会到处给他扔块糖果。
Maybe throw him a candy bar here and there.
如果你能做到这一点，我们就不会陷入困境了。
It'd really, really keep us all out of the hot seat if you could do that.
那太好了。那太好了。
That'd be great. That'd be great.
我真的很感激。比利的权力。
I really appreciate it. Billy Powers.
给你，鲍尔斯。
Here you go, Powers.
谢谢你！
Thank you.
如果你还需要什么就告诉我，好吗?
Let me know if you need anything else, okay?
我打断你们的狂欢了吗?
Did I interrupt the orgy?
请坐。
Have a seat.
这都是给我的吗?
Is this all for me?
还是你这样问候所有的客人?
Or do you greet all your guests like this?
不，不是所有人，只是那些想杀我的人。
No, not all of them, just the ones that try to have me killed.
那家伙，那家伙只是来吓唬你的。
That guy-- That guy was just supposed to scare you.
我看起来很害怕?
I look scared?
是的，你确实需要。
Yeah, you do, actually.
这不是我害怕，孩子。
This ain't me scared, boy.
这是我在生气。
This is me pissed off.
不管怎样，事实是不会改变的。
Well, whatever it is, facts don't change.
你欠保利·罗素十万块，已经过去六周了。
You owe Pauly Russo 100 grand, going on six weeks now.
如果我们想让你死，你就死定了。
If we wanted you dead, that's what you'd be.
接下来的事情是这样的。
Well, here's what's gonna happen.
你们现在要免除我的债务。
You boys are gonna forgive my debt now.
太他妈可爱了。我告诉你吧。
That's pretty fucking cute. I'll tell you what.
你能给我倒杯你在喝的东西吗?
Can you, uh, pour me a glass of whatever that is that you're drinking there?
我在这里跟法律有很多联系。
I got a lot of ties to the law out here.
我打个电话，你和你老板就会有一大堆麻烦我保证你们不会想要的。
I make a phone call, you and your boss have a shitload of trouble that I promise you you don't want.
现在你在威胁我?
Now you're threatening me?
我不喜欢这个。
That, I don't like.
谢谢你的建议。
I appreciate the advice.
你有一周的时间来准备面包。
You got a week to come up with the bread.
昨天的事我很抱歉。
And I'm sorry about yesterday.
那个来找你的人…他一定是停药了。
That guy that came to see you, um... he must've gone off his meds.
我不知道还能跟你说什么。
I don't know what else to tell you.
我现在能说几句吗?
Can I say something now?
这他妈的是你的房子……或者谷仓，不管你管这地方叫什么鬼地方。
It's your fucking house... or barn, or whatever you call this shithole.
我本打算还清我所欠的。
I had every intention of paying what I owe.
我们只是在我的家乡发展得慢一点。
We just move a little slower where I come from.
现在，耐心不是你的强项。
Now, patience ain't your thing.
我想我能理解，但你们太过分了。
I guess I can understand that, but you boys crossed a line.
对我来说，打电话报警告诉他们保利·罗素想要杀了我是件轻而易举的事。
I can't tell you how easy it'd be for me to call the law and tell them Pauly Russo tried to have me killed.
所以别他妈告诉我该做什么不该做什么，尤其是在我自己的谷仓里。
So don't fucking tell me what I will or will not do, especially not in my own barn.
你不能去报警。
You ain't going to the police.
事实上，只有两个人知道昨天发生了什么。
The fact is, only two people really know what happened yesterday.
也许有人知道昨天发生的事。
Might be somebody else knows what happened yesterday.
只是说。
Just saying.
我们会再见的。
I'll see you inbreds around.
-答案是否定的，洛拉-我不懂你，妈妈。
- The answer is no, Lola. - I don't understand you, Mom.
“你感觉怎么样?”“哦，不太好，亲爱的。”
"How are you feeling?" "Oh, not so good, dear."
感觉就像一个生病的胖子坐在我的肺上。
It feels like a diseased fat man is sitting on my lungs.
我问过了，你说你不想谈这个。
I asked and you said you didn't want to talk about it.
-有时“不”意味着“是”。-妈妈，我们要结婚了。
- Sometimes "no" means "yes." - Mom, we're getting married.
-我们要结婚了。-哦，恭喜你。
- We're getting married. - Oh, congratulations.
我在做你一直希望我做的事。
I'm doing what you always wanted me to do.
是的，这就是问题所在。你以为我是白痴?
Yeah, that's the problem. You think I'm an idiot?
你不觉得你突然冒出来找我要钱有点让人讨厌吗?
Don't you find it slightly off-putting that you show up here out of nowhere and ask me for money?
现在?在这个地方?
Now? Here in this place?
-我是来找你的-真的吗?
- I came here to see you. - Oh, really?
因为我快死了，还是因为我多年来反复跟你说的你的演艺事业白费了?
Because I'm dying, or because your acting career that I told you repeatedly over the years was a waste of time didn't work out?
-你赢了。我很久以前就放弃了。
- You won. I gave that up a long time ago.
危地马拉的表演学校。耶稣基督。
Acting school in Guatemala. Jesus Christ.
-哥斯达黎加。-更蠢了。
- Costa Rica. - Even dumber.
我回来不是为了让你嘲笑我糟糕的人生选择，妈妈。
I didn't come back here to be ridiculed for my poor life choices, Mom.
顺便问一下，你上次看我是什么时候?
And by the way, when was the last time you checked in on me?
那不是我的工作。
That's not my job.
女儿呼唤，母亲应声。
A daughter calls, a mother answers.
你知道我妈给我打了多少次电话吗?
You know how many times my mother called me?
你13岁时，你母亲想杀了你。
Your mother tried to kill you when you were 13.
完全正确。
Exactly.
妈妈，我不想失去我在下面的一切。
You know, Mom, I don't want to lose what I have down there.
抛开我们的扯淡不谈，难道你不想让我幸福吗?
All of our bullshit aside, don't you want me to be happy?
我想要的…蟹腿。
I want... crab legs.
——什么?-我不知道为什么。
- What? - I don't know why.
我从来不喜欢吃螃蟹。
I never had a thing for crab.
现在我晚上醒来就想着蟹腿。
Now I'm waking up at night thinking about crab legs.
-嗨，杰基。——嗯?
- Hey, Jackie. - Hmm?
-你喜欢听故事?——确定。
- You like stories? - Sure.
-我有个好主意。-又来了。
- I've got a good one. - Here we go.
你知道他们叫我什么吗?
Do you know what they call me?
黑寡妇。
The Black Widow.
这是正确的。她确实告诉我了。
That's right. She did tell me.
毫米。
Mm.
在说"我愿意"的一年内死了四个丈夫
Four dead husbands within a year of saying "I do."
我只能假设我获得了这个头衔，因为当黑寡妇繁殖时，她经常杀死她的配偶，但这很荒谬，因为我没有和任何一个黑寡妇交配。
I can only assume I earned that title because when the black widow reproduces, she often kills her mate, but that's ridiculous because I didn't mate with any of them.
这个孩子的父亲不知怎么跑掉了。
This one's father got away somehow.
-幸运，幸运。-现在你告诉我…是因为我咬人时会杀人吗?
- Lucky, lucky. - Now you tell me... Is it because I kill people when I bite?
因为他们死后，我要穿黑色衣服吗?
Because when they die, I wear black?
或者是因为我的阴道上或周围有一个红色胎记?
Or could it be that I have a red birthmark somewhere on or around my vagina?
-我的天啊。-我是幸存者，杰姬
- Oh, my God. - I'm a survivor, Jackie.
现在，关于女性黑窗的有趣事实，这是科学。——科学。
Now, interesting fact about the female black window, - and this is science. - Science.
它们注定要比它们的伴侣活得更久。
They're meant to outlive their mates.
,为什么?
And why?
因为她只专注于自己想要的。
It's because she's focused on what she wants.
没有人或任何事能阻止她。
And nobody or nothing is gonna get in her way.
我想要的是一根烟。
And what I want is a cigarette.
还有一些蟹腿。
And some crab legs.
做个乖孩子，杰基。
Be a doll, Jackie.
哦，你想让我…-永远不要让女人乞求。——好的。嗯…-钥匙，亲爱的?-点火。
Oh, you want me to... - Never make a lady beg. - Okay. Uh... - The keys, dear? - In the ignition.
哦,很好。嗯…你还没来得及说"蟹腿"我就回来了?
Oh, good. Um... I'll be back before you can say "crab legs," okay?
-他很帅。-你吓到人了。
- He's handsome. - You scare people.
肯尼·沃尔什喜欢高尔夫。
Kenny Walsh loves golf.
肯尼·沃尔什喜欢上好的咖啡。
Kenny Walsh loves a nice cup of coffee.
肯尼·沃尔什喜欢修剪自己的头发。
Kenny Walsh loves himself some trim.
人谈判?
Who talks?
有钱能使鬼推磨
Money talks.
我是肯尼·沃尔什……肯尼·沃尔什喜欢孩子们
I'm Kenny Walsh... and Kenny Walsh loves the kids.
你会帮我吗，妈妈?
Are you gonna help me, Mom?
你想让我做什么，比利?
So, what do you want me to do, Billy?
把我弄出去。
Get me out of here.
哦,好的。那你要我怎么做?
Oh, okay. Well, and how do you expect that I do that?
告诉我。告诉我。
Tell me. Tell me.
我不知道。我不知道，但我吓坏了，我…我跟我的辅导员谈过，他说我可能会进监狱。哦。
I don't know. I don't know, but I'm freaking out, I'm, uh... I was talking to my counselor and he was saying I could even end up in prison-- Uh-oh! Uh-oh.
是的，那不太好。是的。
Yeah, that's not good. Yeah.
也许你在绑架另一个孩子之前就该想到这一点。
Well, maybe you should've thought about that one before you kidnapped another child.
我他妈的没绑架任何人，妈妈。我告诉过你。
I did not fucking kidnap anyone, Mom. I told you.
我去了查德家，那孩子也在。
I showed up at Chad's, and the kid was there.
是啊，我跟你说过你上次跟查德出去玩的事吗?
Yeah, and what did I tell you about the last fucking time that you hung out with fucking Chad?
——嗯?-你说得对。
- Huh? - You're right.
我再也不去查德家了。
I'll never go to Chad's ever again.
嘿，快点，伙计。我要打个电话。
Yo, hurry up, man. I need to make a phone call.
等一下，是我女朋友。
One sec. It's my girl.
-你会给我找个律师吗?-你知道吗?
- Are you gonna get me a lawyer? - You know what?
我他妈每天都在给你找律师，比利。
I've been spending every fucking day looking for a fucking lawyer for you, Billy.
我都没钱养活自己，好吗?
I can't even afford to feed myself, all right?
嘿，快点，伙计。你一开始没听见吗?
Yo, hurry up, man. You didn't hear me the first time?
-我要打个电话。-是的。连接。
- I need to make a phone call. - Yeah. Connection.
你明天会来看我吗?
Are you gonna come see me tomorrow?
我会尽我所能，好吗?
I'm gonna do the best I fucking can, all right?
对不起，伙计。我刚打完电话。
I'm sorry, man. I just got off the phone.
-我两年前就告诉过你了。-是的。
- I told you that two times ago. - Yeah.
嘿,妈妈。你好吗?
Hey, Mama. How you doing?
我想这是我最后一只螃蟹了。
I think that's my last crab.
那根烟怎么样，杰基小子?
So how about that cigarette, Jackie boy?
你知道吗，妈妈?算了吧。
You know what, Mom? Forget it.
我就知道我不该回来。
I knew I shouldn't have come back here.
但愿我不需要任何人的帮助，更别说我自己的母亲了。
God forbid I need anything from anyone, let alone my own mother.
哦，这一切的戏剧性!
Oh, the drama of it all!
你应该去当演员的。
You should've been a thespian.
如果你没死，我现在就会说些可怕的话。
If you weren't dying, I'd say something horrible right now.
是啊，如果我没死，也许我会在乎。
Yeah, well, if I wasn't dying, maybe I'd give a shit.
-好吧，你想知道真相?——成龙。
- Okay, you want the truth? - Jackie.
-那是我的最爱。——太棒了。
- That's my favorite. - Great.
我15岁的儿子上周因为一件他没做过的事被捕了。
My 15-year-old son was arrested last week for something he did not do.
这是一项严重的指控，他需要律师。
It's a serious charge, and he needs a lawyer.
你女儿和我认识时间不长，好吗?
Your daughter and I have not known each other for very long, okay?
但毫无疑问，她是我一生中遇到的最有趣的人。
But she is, without question, the most interesting human being I have ever met in my life.
我爱她，我想娶她，好吗?
I love her and I want to marry her, okay?
但说实话，我们现在需要那笔钱请律师好让我的孩子出狱，好吗?
But the truth right now, we need that money for a lawyer so we can get my kid out of jail, all right?
-谢谢你的诚实。- -谢谢。
- Well, I thank you for your honesty. -  - Thank you.
-你为什么不把他保释出来?-没有保释。
- But why don't you just bail him out? - There is no bail.
在少管所，是不能保释的。这是不一样的。
Uh, in the juvenile system, there's no bail. It's different.
我得马上把他弄出来。
I need to get him out, like, now.
请律师要花多少钱?
So how much does this lawyer cost?
嗯…我猜大概是25000美元吧?
Uh... I'm guessing like $25,000?
你猜?
You're guessing?
我一找到律师就知道了。
I will know the second I secure the lawyer.
好吧，你这样做，等你回来，-我会给你开张支票。-哦，谢谢。
Well, you do that, and when you come back, - I will write you a check. - Oh, thank you.
当然，除非我改变主意。
Unless, of course, I change my mind.
是的,女士。是的,女士。
Yes, ma'am. Yes, ma'am.
等待。
Wait.
哦!
Oh!
-我爱你，儿子-我也爱你。
- I love you, son. - I love you too.
我非常爱你们俩。
I love the both of you very much.
哦,上帝。他是一个守门员。
Oh, God. He's a keeper.
这对你来说意义重大。
That means a lot coming from you.
啧啧。好吧。
Tsk. All right.
对不起，我现在不能给你钱。
I'm sorry I can't give you any money right now.
不过，我会为你即将成为继子的人出资，因为，出于某种原因，这样做似乎是对的但除此之外，我的直觉告诉我不是这样的。
I will, however, put up the money for your soon-to-be stepson, because, for some reason, it seems like the right thing to do but beyond that, my instincts are telling me otherwise.
我知道我们彼此不了解，洛拉。
I know we don't understand each other, Lola.
我们从来没有。
We never did.
但如果你能接受我所做的一切…连我自己都无法解释的事情这将是我最后的愿望。
But if you could accept the things that I do... that even I can't explain... that would be my final wish.
你能做到吗?
Can you do that?
我可以试试。
I can try.
她才认识你两分钟!
She's known you for two minutes!
螃蟹腿，一段多愁善感的独白，然后她就准备给你开张支票了?
Crab legs, a sappy abridged monologue, and she's ready to write you a check?
你知道这些年来我问她要过多少次钱吗?
Do you know how many times I've asked her for money over the years?
-我可以想象。-我的一生。
- I can imagine. - My whole life.
我这辈子，她都不把我当回事。
My whole fucking life, she's treated me like shit.
“我很有才华，妈妈。我真的很擅长我的工作。
"I'm talented, Mom. I'm really good at what I do.
我所需要的只是一张去纽约的机票，还有一点现金。”
All I need is a plane ticket to New York City, and a little bit of cash."
不。滚开，亲爱的。
Nope. Fuck off, darling.
-我真的很抱歉-你为什么道歉?你得到了你想要的。
- Look, I'm really sorry. - What are you sorry for? You got what you wanted.
布拉沃。你应该去当演员。
Bravo. You should've been the actor.
听着，你值得更好的，就这样?但我的孩子也是。
Look, you deserve better, period, okay? But so does my kid.
我知道你现在很难过，但我求你了，求求你，求求你在这件事上支持我。
I know you're upset right now, but I'm begging you, please, please stick with me on this.
我还想让你知道我刚才说的话是认真的。
I also want you to know I meant what I said back there.
哪一部分?
Which part?
我真的得去打个电话。
I really gotta get to a phone.
抱歉，但我得，我得去打个电话。
I'm sorry, but I gotta-- I gotta get to a phone.
这些人到底是干什么的?
What the fuck do these people do?
她给有钱人口交。
She blows rich guys.
这是女孩母亲的房子。
It's the girl's mother's house.
我他妈的一整天都在外面。什么都没有。
I'm out here all fucking day. Nothing.
你真觉得沃尔特会去报警吗?
You really think Walter is gonna go to the police?
我他妈不能太确定，对吧?
I can't be too fucking sure, can I?
但我他妈百分百确定的是我他妈不想知道。
But what I can be 100% fucking sure is that I don't want to fucking find out.
我叔叔带着犯罪指控回家了，我现在只需要面对谋杀指控，好吗?
My uncle back fucking home with the RICO charges, all I need now is to face a fucking murder rap, okay?
所以帮我个忙，去找该死的杰基让他明白，让他明白，我需要他去自首，如果他这么做了，等他出狱后，
So do me a fucking favor, and find fucking Jackie and make him understand, make him fucking understand, I need him to turn himself in, and if he does that, when he gets out of fucking jail,
如果他他妈的出狱了，我们会照顾他的，好吗?帮我吧。
if he gets out of fucking jail, we're gonna take care of him, okay? Do that for me.
-那孩子怎么办?-去他的孩子，好吗?
- What about the kid? - Fuck the kid, okay?
-那船已经起航了。-搞什么鬼?
- That ship sailed. - What the fuck?
-走，走，走!——什么?
- Go, go, go! - What?
-快!直走!-你在干什么?
- Gun it! Go straight! - What are you doing?
枪了!走吧!走吧!走吧!走吧!
Gun it! Go! Go! Go! Go!
这他妈是个破案。
This is a fucking bust.
我要回到我的生活中去。
I need to get back to my fucking life.
我想我知道他下一步可能去哪了。
I think I got an idea where he might be headed next.
这才对，多姆。现在，照着你说的做，让他明白。
Now you're talking, Dom. Now, go follow that idea and fucking make him understand.
——是吗?-是的。
- Yeah? - Yeah.
明天，我要去见沃尔特。
Tomorrow, I'm gonna go up, I'm gonna see Walter.
我要自己处理这破事。
I'm gonna take care of this bullshit by myself.
小心。那该死的乡巴佬准备开战了。
Careful. That fucking hillbilly's ready for war over there.
显然，我是和平前来的。
I'm gonna come in peace, obviously.
-一定会很棒的。——正确的。
- It's gonna be fucking amazing. - Right.
你相信这些鬼话?我要去讨钱吗?
You believe this shit? I gotta go beg for fucking money?
我要去讨我的钱吗?家里的人听到这个，都会说"等等，保利他妈怎么了"
I gotta go beg for my fucking money? Anybody at home hears about this, they're like, "Wait, what the fuck happened to Pauly?"
“我不知道。他搬到俄克拉荷马州去了，变成了一个婊子。”
"I don't know. He moved out to Oklahoma and became a cunt."
他妈的。
Fuck.
上帝啊，泰勒。你在这里拨号吗?
Jesus Christ, Taylor. What are you, on dial-up here?
如果你不喜欢我的东西，那就去别的地方。
If you don't like my shit, then go somewhere else.
事实上，你应该去别的地方，带上这个婊子。
In fact, you should just go elsewhere and you should take this whore with you.
-你说什么?-求你了，泰勒?
- Excuse me? - Please, Taylor?
这是家事。我不知道你在这里做什么。
This is a family matter. I don't know what you're doing here.
再叫我婊子，看看会发生什么。
Call me a whore again and see what happens.
-你是谁?-朋友。
- And who are you? - A friend.
这是奇怪的。杰基没有朋友。
That's weird. Jackie doesn't have any friends.
-泰勒，求你了?-你想知道为什么吗?
- Can you please, Taylor? - You want to know why?
-我没有。-因为他是个大混蛋。
- I don't. - It's because he's a really big asshole.
-一个大屁眼。——可爱。可爱。
- A big, gaping asshole. - Lovely. Lovely.
你想听听我的建议吗?-我当然不知道。
- Would you like some advice? - I definitely don't.
我认为你应该做的是，你应该跑，跑得越快越好。
Well, what I think you should do is, you should run and run as fast as you can.
如果你已经怀孕了，那就左转，直接去诊所。-好了，够了。
And if you're pregnant already, then make a left - and go straight to the clinic. - All right, that's enough.
我知道你在这里的生活一团糟，我也不想，但你再这样下去，我就把你的牙打烂。
I can see that your life's shit here, and I'd rather not, but keep it up, and I'll knock your fucking teeth in.
-这是威胁吗?-不然还能是什么?
- Is that a threat? - What the fuck else would it be?
沃尔什先生，我叫杰姬·鲍尔斯?
Hey, uh, Mr. Walsh, my-my name is Jackie Powers, okay?
我儿子是比利·鲍尔斯。
My son is Billy Powers.
他目前在哈斯克尔监狱等待拘留听证会，听证会将在两天后举行。
He's currently at Haskell awaiting a detention hearing, which is in two days.
请尽快给我回电话。
Please call me back at your earliest convenience.
我的电话是918-793-1248。
My number is 918-793-1248.
非常感谢。
Thank you very much.
你为什么要给我电话?
Why did you give my number?
-我的天啊。-这是给你儿子的，泰勒
- Oh, my God. - It's for your son, Taylor.
好吧。
Okay.
嗯哼。
Ahem.
-打扰一下。原谅我。-说吧。
- Excuse me. Excuse me. - Go ahead.
哦,他妈的。
Oh, fuck.
他妈的,他妈的。走后门，现在。
Fuck, fuck. Back door, now.
我们走吧。出去，出去，出去。后门。走吧，走吧。我们走吧。我们得走了。
Let's go. Out, out, out. Back door. Let's go, let's go. Let's go. We gotta go.
-你在说什么?-现在，现在，现在。
- What are you talking about? - Now, now, now.
-听我说。听我说。——什么?
- Listen to me. Listen to me. - What?
-那是多姆，好吗?请……——哦。怎么啦？
- That is Dom, okay? Please... - Oh. What?
如果你说见过我，比利就死定了。
If you mention that you've seen me, Billy is fucked.
做正确的事。别惹我，泰勒。
Do the right thing. Don't fuck with me, Taylor.
别惹我。做正确的事，向我保证你不会提起你见过我。
Don't fuck with me. Do the right thing and give me your word you will not mention that you've seen me.
好吧。走了。
Okay. Go.
-给我滚出去。-谢谢。谢谢你！谢谢你！
- Get the fuck out of here. - Thank you. Thank you. Thank you.
-是谁?-是警察。
- Who is it? - It's the police.
是的,对的。
Yeah, right.
他在哪里?
Where is he?
谁?
Who?
得了吧，别装可爱了。杰基。
Come on, don't be cute. Jackie.
我没见过他。
I haven't seen him.
那是什么?
What was that?
好吧，就是他，好吗?
All right, it was him, okay?
但我真的不知道他要去哪里。
But I really have no idea where he was going.
我为什么不相信你?
Why don't I believe you?
因为你就是个混蛋，这就是原因。
Because you're a fucking asshole, that's why.
好吧，泰勒，别胡扯了。
All right, Taylor, with the bullshit.
好吧，你就这么走了?
All right, you're just gonna leave?
是啊，我不是为了这个来的。
Yeah, I didn't come here for that.
你知道你的问题在哪里吗?
You know what your problem is?
你把我当狗屎是有原因的。
You treat me like shit for a reason.
不，我把你当狗屎是因为你是个混蛋大多数时候都是你活该。
No, I treat you like shit because you're an asshole and you deserve it most of the time.
不，你还在气我选了杰姬而不是你。
No, you're still mad that I chose Jackie and not you.
选择成龙吗?
Chose Jackie?
你什么都没选。看看这该死的地方。
You didn't choose shit. Look at this fucking place.
我来告诉你为什么你和杰姬而不是我在一起。
I'll tell you why you ended up with Jackie and not me.
这真他妈简单。
It's real fucking simple.
你犯了个错误。
You made a mistake.
没什么大不了的，但别把我当成坏人。
It's no big deal, but don't treat me like I'm the bad guy.
你想让我留下来和你做爱…让我留下来。
You want me to stay and throw a fuck in you... just tell me to stay.
这家伙总有他妈毛病。
Always gotta be a fucking thing with this one.
他们的蟹腿都卖完了。
They were all out of crab legs.
我只是不敢相信你和那个女人有个孩子。
I just can't believe you had a child with that woman.
就像，故意的。
Like, on purpose.
你真该看看她二十年前的样子。
Yeah, well, you should've seen her 20 years ago.
无论什么。相同的大脑。
Whatever. Same brain.
怎么啦？
What?
嗯…
Uh...
你有没有…你…你…你喜欢我吗?
Do you, um... Do you-do you... Do you like me?
如果他们明天不让我见你儿子怎么办?
What if they don't let me in to see your son tomorrow?
-他们会的-我们姓不一样。
- They-- they will. - We have different last names.
正确的。你知道那地方有多少孩子的父母姓一样吗?都不是。
Right. Do you know how many kids in that place have two parents with the same last names? None of them.
但如果冒充别人的母亲去拜访是一种行为呢?
But what if impersonating someone's mother to visit is, like, a thing?
-不是的。-你怎么知道?
- It's not. - How do you know, though?
因为我是在那里长大的。
Because I grew up in there.
那个人，多姆?他太。
That guy, Dom? Him too.
我们13岁时在那里相遇。
We met in there when we were 13 years old.
你看到他的生活了吗?
You see what he's doing with his life?
少管所里没有改过自新。
There's no rehabilitation in the juvenile system.
这地方只会毁了你，就这样。
The place just fucks you up, period.
我会帮你把比利救出来。
I'm gonna help you get Billy out of there.
啊哈。那你是说你喜欢我还是…?
Ah-ha. So, is that-that a yes, you do like me or...?
你真想玩这个游戏吗?
You really want to play this game?
一个练习吗?是啊，为什么不呢?
An exercise? Yeah, why not?
好吧。
Okay.
-那我就玩。——好的。
- I'll play then. - Okay.
你在做什么?
What are you doing?
我不只是喜欢你，杰姬。
I don't just like you, Jackie.
我爱你。
I love you.
你走进那家小饭馆的那一刻，我的心就跳了一拍。
The second you walked into that greasy spoon, my heart skipped a beat.
那一刻我就知道事情会永远改变。
I knew in that moment things were gonna change forever.
我知道我要与之共度余生的男人刚刚走进了我的生活。
I knew the man I was gonna spend the rest of my days with just walked into my life.
但你开枪打了厨师。
But then you shot the cook.
-很好，对吧?-是的。
- Pretty good, right? - Yeah.
我说过我有天赋。
I told you I had talent.
非常好。很神奇的。
That was very good. Amazing.
我们要进去吗?
Should we go inside?
嗯…里面只有一张床，所以我想让你睡一会儿。
Uh... There's just one bed in there, so I figured I'd let you get some sleep.
我想我就在这里睡一会儿吧。
I'll just crash out here a little bit, I guess.
-好的，晚安。-不，我是说…
- Okay, good night. - No, I mean...
真是个白痴。
Such a fucking idiot.
萝拉?
Lola?
搞什么鬼?
What the fuck?
“别担心。我去买甜甜圈和咖啡了。
"Don't worry. Just went to get donuts and coffee.
爱,萝拉。”
Love, Lola."
谢谢你！
Thank you.
耶稣基督。
Jesus Christ.
——你好吗?-嘿，律师打电话来了吗?
- Hello? -  - Hey,, uh, did the lawyer call yet?
不，不，不。现在是早上七点半。他还没打电话来。
No, uh-uh, no. It's 7:30 in the morning. He hasn't called yet.
好吧。昨晚我走后，多姆怎么了?
Okay. What happened with Dom after I left last night?
-哦，还不错。-还不错吧?
- Oh, it wasn't bad. - It wasn't bad?
你这是什么意思?
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
意思是他来过，问你在不在。
It means that he came in, he asked if you were here.
-我拒绝了，然后他就走了-别这样，你个婊子。拿到地址。
- I said no, then he left. - Come on, you bitch. Get the address.
我现在真的很累，所以你能让我醒醒吗?
And I'm really tired right now, so can you please let me wake up?
无论如何,泰勒。拜托，如果那个律师打电话来，马上告诉我。这很重要，好吗?
Whatever, Taylor. Please, just, if that lawyer calls, let me know immediately. It's very important, okay?
我在11街的西部酒店。街。
I'm at the Western Inn on 11th. Street.
129房间，好吗?
Room 129, okay?
好吧。
Okay.
太好了。谢谢你！
Great. Thank you.
该死的怪人。
Fucking weirdo.
事情已经完全失控了，沃尔特。
Things have gotten way out of hand here, Walter.
好吧，有件事我们可以达成共识。
Well, there's something we can agree on.
这不是我的本意。
It was never my intention.
好吧。既然你提到了，那你的目的到底是什么?
Okay. Well, now that you mentioned it, what exactly was your intention?
最重要的是，你跟我下了很多重大的赌注。
Bottom line is, you made some very serious bets with me.
-你输了。-我对此没有意见。
- You lost. - I don't have a problem with that.
显然你知道，因为我现在和你在一起。
Apparently, you do, because I'm here with you now.
我还我的债。我只是需要更多时间。
I pay my debts. I just needed more time.
但我们现在不是在说我，对吧?
But we're not talking about me now, are we?
我们说的是你和你的意图。
We're talking about you and your intention.
你知道的…沃尔特，在我看来，不管那个混蛋做了什么，他都太过分了。
You know... Look, Walter, as far as I'm concerned, whatever that fucking jerk-off did, he was way out of line.
这不是我想要的好吗?但这已经不是我的问题了。
It's not what I wanted, okay? But that is no longer my problem.
我已经告诉过你了，我们说话这会儿他正在去自首的路上。好吧?
I already told you, he's on his way to turn himself in as we speak. Okay?
现在，我相信你知道那个想杀你的混蛋下半辈子都要在监狱里吃垃圾火腿三明治，你一定会感到些许安慰，沃尔特。
Now, I'm sure you take some kind of fucking comfort in knowing the jerk-off who tried to kill you is gonna spend the rest of his life behind bars eating shitty ham sandwiches, Walter.
我是来和你和平解决问题的，伙计。
I'm here to work this out with you, man, peacefully.
这是礼貌，沃尔特。
That's a courtesy, Walter.
请不要把它误认为其他东西。
Please don't mistake it for anything else.
你知道怎么养牛吗?
You know anything about raising cattle?
我来自布鲁克林。
I'm from Brooklyn.
这不是一件复杂的事情。
It isn't a complicated business.
我和他们打交道。它们属于我。
I deal with them. They belong to me.
卖的时候到了，我就让他们走了。
Time comes to sell, I let them go.
我的某只阉牛生病了，或者其中一只在着陆时不听话，这是我的责任，这是我的责任。
One of my steers gets sick, or one of them just don't do right when they land, that's my responsibility, and I own that.
好吧。
Okay.
我在这里待了很长时间，干这行快40年了。
I've been in these parts a long time now, almost 40 years doing what I do.
我有很多朋友，律师什么的。
I got a lot of friends, law and otherwise.
你是这里的客人。
You are a guest here.
现在我明白了…你可能对事情有自己的看法，但是…不幸的是，你是否觉得对我们降落的地方负有责任并不重要。
Now I understand... you might have your own feelings about things, but... whether or not you feel responsible for where we've landed is unfortunately irrelevant.
我这么问只是出于礼貌。
I only asked as a courtesy.
别把它当成别的东西了。
Let's not mistake that for something else.
你看到…一股力量扭转了局势。
You see... a force has swung the tide here.
虽然我很感谢你的来访，保利
And while I appreciate the visit, Pauly...
我说话算数。
I stand by my word.
我什么都不欠你。
I don't owe you a goddamn thing.
你真的想和我一起走这条路吗，沃尔特?
You really want to take this road with me, Walter?
欢迎你来找，我的朋友。
You are welcome to find out, my friend.
嘿!
Hey!
他妈的!
Fuck!
事情是这样的，杰姬。
Here's what's gonna happen, Jackie.
你要去自首。
You're gonna turn yourself in.
你要承认你杀了餐厅里的那个人，就这样吧。
You're gonna confess to killing the guy in the diner, and that's the end of it.
好吧。好吧。
Okay. Okay.
-比利呢?-呆在原地别动。
- What about Billy? - Stay right the fuck where you are.
来吧。
Come on.
比利是，呃…他不再是我们的问题了。
Billy is, uh... He's not our problem anymore.
好吧，那不行。操。
Okay, then no. Get fucked.
- "不，去死吧"?-是的。
- "No, get fucked"? - Yeah.
-你他妈是鹦鹉吗?-小心点，杰姬。
- What are you, a fucking parrot? - Watch it, Jackie.
我现在该怕你了就因为你有枪吗?搞什么鬼?
Oh, I'm supposed to be scared of you now because you got a gun? What the fuck?
杰克，这是你自找的。
Jack, you got yourself in this fucking situation.
我说的不是那个。我说的是你，波士顿来的硬汉。
I'm not talking about that. I'm talking about you, big tough guy from Boston.
-你来中环的第一天…-去你妈的。
- Your first day in Central... - Fuck you.
．..你看起来都要尿裤子了。如果不是我，你在那个地方连两秒钟都坚持不了。
...you looked like you were gonna piss yourself. If it wasn't for me, you wouldn't have lasted two seconds in that place.
你不过是个跑腿的。
You are nothing but an errand boy, ho.
嘿，你真是个混蛋。你知道我怎么想吗?
Hey, you're a punchy cocksucker. You know what I think?
我觉得你那该死的脑袋被打了太多次了，你的记忆一团糟。-哦，是吗?
I think you got hit one too many times in that dopey fucking head of yours, - and your memory is mush. - Oh, is that right?
-是的。——是吗?
- Yeah. - Yeah?
你是个忘恩负义的小混蛋，你知道吗?
You're an ungrateful little motherfucker, you know that?
-我现在就该干死你。-是吗?
- I ought to fuck you up right now. - Oh, yeah?
带不带枪，硬汉?
With or without the gun, tough guy?
这他妈的不是戒指，杰克。
This ain't the fucking ring, Jack.
我看你敢不敢把枪放下。
I fucking dare you to put that gun down.
这不是我第一次搞砸你了。
It won't be the first time I fucked you up.
-我现在就打爆你。-好吧。让我看看。
- I'll bust your fucking hole right now. - All right. Let me see it.
-来吧。-好吧，等等。等一等。
- Come on. - Okay, whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
我能先把衣服穿上吗?
Can I put my clothes on first?
请做。
Please do.
哦。
Oh.
——甜甜圈?-我们该走了，好吗?
- Donut? - We should probably go, okay?
现在。
Now.
-很酷的衣服。——谢谢。来吧。
- Cool outfit. - Thanks. Come on.
-你要穿这个吗?——没有。
- Are you gonna wear that? - No.
-好吧。-听…我就自己来了，好吗?
- All right. - Listen... I'd be doing this myself, okay?
但鉴于我目前正因谋杀被通缉，我觉得这不是个好主意。
But on the off chance I'm currently wanted for murder, I don't think it's a good idea.
-可能不会。-听着，你不是真的在犯罪
- Probably not. - Look, you're not-- you're not actually committing a crime.
不，我很确定我是。
No, I'm pretty sure I am.
好吧，没错，但这就像乱穿马路。
Okay, fine, yes, but it's like jaywalking.
这是违法的，但还是有人这么做?
It's illegal, but people do it, you know?
-知道了。-你会很好的，好吗?
- Got it. - You're gonna be great, okay?
还有，别忘了要一份他的档案。
And please, do not forget to get a copy of his files.
根据法律，他们必须给你。
By law, they have to give them to you.
-给他母亲。-不管是谁。无论什么。
- To his mother. - To whoever. Whatever.
你明白我的意思，好吗?
You get what I'm saying, okay?
你是个演员。的行为。
You're an actor. Act.
-还有别的吗?——没有。是的。
- Anything else? - No. Yes.
告诉他我爱他，一切都会好起来的。
Tell him I love him, and everything's gonna be fine.
——请。——好的。
- Please. - Okay.
快点。告诉我什么时候。
Hurry up. Tell me when.
-今晚7点。-哦，不。伙计……哥们，上个星期二之后，我周五才会走路。
- Tonight, 7:00. - Oh, no. Dude... Dude, I couldn't walk until Friday after last Tuesday.
是的，她块头很大。
Yeah, she was huge.
我是说，那么大的女孩，长得像她?
I mean, a girl that big, who looks like her?
她的肩膀像约翰·艾维。
She had shoulders like John Elway.
——你好吗?-真是个大女孩，T。
- Hello? - That was a big girl, T.
-什么时候?-七点，宝贝。下午7点
- What time? - 7:00, baby. 7:00 P.M.
下午7点
7:00 P.M.
我是来探望我儿子的，比利·鲍尔斯。
I'm here-- I'm here to visit my son, Billy Powers.
耶稣。等一下，约翰。
Jesus. Hang on a sec, John.
萝拉…Brisky。洛拉Brisky。
Lola... Brisky. Lola Brisky.
是啊，只是来看我儿子。
Yeah, just visiting my-my son.
好吧。
All right.
填一下这个。
Fill this out.
把你所有的东西都放在那个储物柜里。
Take all your belongings and put them in that locker.
我还需要一份他的档案副本。
I'm also gonna need a copy of his files.
你得在探视后和住院医生谈谈。
You'll have to talk to intake after the visit.
她听起来很性感，伙计。
She sounds hot, man.
哦，伙计，她很性感。
Oh, dude, she was hot.
她他妈的叫什么名字?
What the fuck was her name?
-她在抽烟。——操。
- She was smoking. - Fuck.
是的。洛拉Brisky。
Yeah. Lola Brisky.
我跟你说，搭档。
Let me tell you something, partner.
肯尼·沃尔什是镇上代理青少年案件最多的人。
Kenny Walsh has represented more juvenile cases than anyone in this town.
肯尼·沃尔什并不完美，但是…他已经很接近了。
Kenny Walsh is not perfect, but... he's pretty damn close.
肯尼·沃尔什在地检署待了15年。的办公室。
Now, Kenny Walsh spent 15 years in the D. A.'s office.
这没什么坏处。
That doesn't hurt.
不，我在你的网站上看到的。
No, I-I-I read that on your site.
先说清楚，你是谁?
Just to be clear, who are you?
肯尼·沃尔什报道。
I'm Kenny Walsh.
你他妈以为我是谁?
Who the fuck do you think I am?
太好了。好吧，我只是澄清一下。
Great. Okay, I was just clarifying.
今天早上我打了你留的那个电话，但是没人接。
I did call that number that you left on my service several times this morning, but no answer.
正确的。对，这就对了。
Right. Right, that figures.
我不知道这是什么意思，但显然你有问题，否则你也不会来这里。
I'm not sure what that means, but clearly you have some problems, or else you wouldn't be here.
肯尼·沃尔什的事说够了。我能帮你什么忙吗?
But enough about Kenny Walsh. How can I help you?
好吧，我儿子比利·鲍尔斯，就像我在你服务时提到的，他的拘留听证会在明天，好吗?
Okay, um, uh, my son, as I mentioned on your service, Billy Powers, his detention hearing is tomorrow, okay?
我知道这很仓促，但我向你保证，他是个好孩子。——嗯。
I know that that is very short notice, - but I assure you, he is a good kid. - Uh-huh.
从来没惹过什么法律纠纷。
Never been in any trouble with the law whatsoever.
好吧。哇，哇，哇。
Okay. Whoa, whoa, whoa.
-别说了。——好的。
- Stop right there. - Okay.
肯尼·沃尔什不是法官。
Kenny Walsh is not the judge.
好与坏，对他来说都无所谓。
Good or bad, doesn't make a difference to him.
好吧。
Okay.
我来问你。人谈判?
Let me ask you. Who talks?
有钱能使鬼推磨
Money talks.
啊。是的。正确的。
Ah. Yeah. Right.
-你有他的档案吗?——没有。
- You have his case file? - No.
但我会在今天之内拿到他的案件卷宗和一张两万美元的支票。
But I will have his case file and a check for you for $20,000 by the end of the day.
——今天好吗?——今天。
- Today? - Today.
肯尼·沃尔什会来。
Kenny Walsh will be here.
太好了。
Great.
一旦我拿到上面提到的东西，你儿子也会。
Once I get that aforementioned in my hand, your son will be too.
这是一件好事。
And that's a good thing.
肯尼·沃尔什总是能搞定。
Kenny Walsh always gets it done.
那太好了。
That's-that's very good.
好吧。谢谢你！
Okay. Thank you.
-随便拿根棒棒糖吧。——好的。
- Um, help yourself with a lollipop. - Okay.
比利，我是你妈妈。
I'm your mother, Billy.
你爸爸在外面，他说他非常爱你。
Your father is outside, and he says he loves you very much.
我在给律师拿你的文件。
I'm just getting your files for the lawyer.
你明白吗?
Do you understand?
-是的。——好。
- Yeah. - Good.
我去拿你的文件。
I'll go get your files.
我真的很害怕。你能跟我谈谈吗?
I'm really scared. Will you just talk to me?
-是的。-谢谢。
- Yeah. - Thank you.
我没做错什么。
I didn't do anything wrong.
我去的时候他们已经绑架了那孩子。
They'd already kidnapped the kid when I showed up.
我只是不属于这里。
I just don't belong here.
是的，我相信你。
Yeah, I believe you.
我的妈妈…我是说，那个女人。
My mom... I mean, that woman.
我已经两周没见过她了。我不——
I haven't seen her in two weeks. I don't--
我只是，我只是不想待在这里。
I just-- I just don't want to stay here.
你爸爸正在研究。
Your dad's working on it.
哦。哦,太棒了。你这是在安慰我吗?
Oh. Oh, great. That's supposed to make me feel better?
-他真的很爱你。-我知道。
- Hey, he really loves you. - I know he does.
-他…他只是…——什么?
- He's-- He's just... - What?
他一直都很操蛋。
He's just always been such a fuck up.
我是说，你肯定知道，对吧?
I mean, you must know that, right?
其实我觉得你爸爸很特别，但别告诉他我这么说，好吗?
I actually think your dad's pretty special, but don't tell him I said so, okay?
我不会的。
I won't.
顺便问一下，你有糖尿病吗?
By the way, are you diabetic?
不。
No.
我看起来胖吗?
Do I look fat?
这是非常非常非常……该死的尴尬。
This is very, very, very... fucking embarrassing.
-你告诉我?-是的，多姆。
- You're telling me? - Yes, Dom.
我他妈的告诉你。你知道为什么吗?两个原因。
I'm fucking telling you. You know why? Two reasons.
首先，你他妈是唯一坐在我前面的人，另一个原因是，你他妈是我尴尬的原因。
First, you're the only fuck sitting in front of me, and the other reason is, because you're the fucking cause of me being embarrassed.
我会再去找杰基的。
I'll find Jackie again.
我知道你会找到杰基的，这次，你要干掉他。
Oh, I know you're gonna find Jackie, and this time, you're gonna whack him.
来吧，保利。给我滚出去。
Come on, Pauly. Get the fuck outta here.
看着我的脸。看着我的脸。
Look at my fucking face. Look at my fucking face.
你看我像在开玩笑吗?你觉得我像在开玩笑吗?
I look like I'm joking to you? Do I look like I'm joking to you?
我一开始就不该听你的关于这孩子的事。
I should've never listened to you in the first place about this fucking kid to begin with.
这是我两天前对你说的，而你说别他妈告诉我我说了什么。别他妈告诉我我说了什么。
That's what I said to you two days ago, and you said-- Don't fucking tell me what I said. Don't fucking tell me what I said.
我知道我他妈说了什么。我不能改变主意?
I know what I fucking said. I can't change my mind?
我的天啊。听我说。听我说。
Jesus fucking Christ. Listen to me. Listen to me.
我他妈怎么了?
What the fuck happened to me?
我是说，看看我穿了什么。我他妈带了个皮带扣。
I mean, look what I'm wearing. I'm wearing a fucking belt buckle.
我以我死去的母亲发誓，我能感觉到我的自尊从我的屁眼里融化了。
I swear on my dead mother, I can feel my fucking ego melting out of my-my-my asshole.
我告诉你，保利。
I'm telling you, Pauly.
我们照顾好杰姬的孩子，给他找个律师，整件事就结束了。——没有。不。
We take care of Jackie's kid, we get him a lawyer - and this whole thing ends. - No. No.
他妈的不。不。不。他妈的没有，没有。
Fucking no. No. No. Fucking no and no.
也没有!也没有!
And no! And no!
你他妈的别告诉我!我他妈的告诉你!
You don't fucking tell me! I fucking tell you!
你他妈的什么都不告诉我。
You don't tell me fucking nothing.
我陷入这该死的困境都是因为你。
I'm in this fucking jam to begin with because of you.
-是的。我现在明白了。-哦，很好。好吧，聪明的家伙。
- Yeah. I'm clear on that now. - Oh, good. Okay, wise ass.
小心点，好吗?
Watch yourself, okay?
你还想说清楚点什么吗?我来告诉你。
You want to be clear on something else? I'll tell you.
好家伙他妈的保利完蛋了。
Nice guy fucking Pauly is done.
我要开车去那个混蛋牛仔的牧场亲自一枪崩了他的头。
I'm gonna drive out to that cowboy cocksucker's fucking ranch and I am personally gonna shoot him in the fucking head.
但你一定要找到那个小贱人然后你他妈一枪毙了他就像我一枪打死另一个人一样。
But you are gonna find that little cunt and you're gonna fucking shoot him the same way I shoot the other fucking guy.
明白了吗?
Are we clear?
哦,上帝。怎么样?
Oh, God. How'd it go?
-你有个好孩子。-哦，真漂亮。
- You have a good kid. - Oh, it's beautiful.
好了，我们准时到了。我们走吧。
All right, we're good on time. Let's go.
-希望她没改变主意-请不要这么说。
- Hopefully, she didn't change her mind. - Please don't say that.
哦,耶稣。
Oh, Jesus.
这该死的东西。
This fucking thing.
好吧，我是个出色的司机。
Okay, I'm an excellent driver.
我很抱歉。
I'm so sorry.
她在吃蟹腿。她看起来很好。
She was eating crab legs. She seemed fine.
我对天发誓，她是故意的。
I swear to God, she did this on purpose.
死的吗?
Died?
是的。
Yeah.
带我回家。
Take me home.
我不认为这是个好主意。
I don't think that's a good idea.
很好,然后。送我去机场。
Fine, then. Take me to the airport.
那又怎样，你觉得我们没机会拿到钱了吗?
So what, you don't think there's a chance that we can still get the money?
你他妈在开玩笑吗?
Are you fucking kidding me?
-这是个合理的问题。-嘿，当然。
- It's a legitimate question. - Hey, yeah, sure.
我们要做的就是尽快结婚。
All we have to do is just get married real quick.
好吧，我们真的能做到吗?
Okay, is that something we can actually do?
天啊，我不是认真的，你这个变态。
Oh, my-- I wasn't being serious, you fucking sociopath.
如果真有那么容易，我早就嫁给别的混蛋了。-太好了。
If it were that easy, I could've married some other asshole - a long time ago. - That's very nice.
你知道，控制遗嘱的人，他们有指令。
You know, the people who control the will, they have instructions.
这需要时间。我又不是一说"我愿意"就能得到一大块
It takes time. It's not like I get a chunk the second I say "I do."
我只是在想该怎么做，好吗?
I'm just trying to figure out what to do, okay?
郑重声明，我愿意嫁给你。
And for the record, so you know, I would marry you.
我知道你会的。你他妈就是个反社会分子。
I know you would. You're a fucking sociopath.
你能不能别这么叫我?
Will you stop calling me that?
你在医院对我妈说的那些屁话你说你有多喜欢我你想和我共度余生?
All the shit that you said to my mom at the hospital about how much you really like me and you want to spend the rest of your life with me?
只有某种人才会做出那种事。
It takes a certain kind of person to do some shit like that.
哦,好的。你在汽车旅馆的事呢?
Oh, okay. What about you at the motel?
“我爱你，杰基。在这个小饭馆里，我们相遇了
"I love you, Jackie. In this greasy spoon when we met eyes,"
还有那些屁话，不管你说了什么?
and all that bullshit, whatever it was you said, huh?
这是不同的。我们只是在闹着玩。
That's different. We were just messing around.
-不，不。我不会在这方面浪费时间。-随便了，好吗?随你的便!
- No, no. I don't mess around that way. - Whatever, okay? Whatever!
我他妈的要离开这里。
I'm getting the fuck out of here.
你去找你的律师，开我妈妈的车，也许他会开。
You just go to your lawyer, take my mom's car, maybe he'll take it.
-太好了!-我他妈的要离开这里。
- That's great! - I'm getting the fuck out of here.
太好了!我很乐意，但我的律师已经关门了。
That's great! I'd love to do that, except that my lawyer's fucking closed.
我知道，因为我们刚经过那里。
I know that because we just passed the place.
抱歉让你久等了。死去的妈妈每次都能抓住你。
Well, sorry for the hold up. Dead mom gets you every time.
哦，别废话了!好像这是一个巨大的损失。
Oh, cut the crap! Like it was a big loss.
反正你也恨她。
You hated her anyway.
他妈的。
Fuck.
好了，你现在得停车了。
Okay, you're gonna have to stop the car now.
滚远点，假装我不存在。
Get the fuck out of it, and pretend that I don't exist.
太好了。太好了，因为我有个新计划，而且不包括你。——太棒了。
That's great. That's great, because I have a new plan - and it doesn't involve you. - Great.
好吧?明天我就要走进法庭，带上这个，带上我儿子我要杀出一条血路，离开那个悲惨的地方。-太棒了。
Okay? I'm gonna go into that courtroom tomorrow, I'm gonna bring this, I'm gonna get my son and I'm gonna shoot my way out - of that miserable place. - That's brilliant.
也许你该先弄点子弹学学怎么用，你个白痴。
Maybe you should get some bullets and learn how to use it first, you fucking moron.
他妈的。
Fuck.
顺便说一句，你什么事都可以做。
You're welcome, by the way, for everything.
你能看着我吗?
Can you look at me?
谢谢你！
Thank you.
我这辈子从来没有人像你这几天这么关心我。
No one in my entire life has ever been there for me the way you have the last couple of days.
无论如何，我希望你不要误会，但我真的爱你。
For whatever it's worth, and I hope you don't take this the wrong way, but I really do love you.
我得去照顾我的孩子了。
I gotta go take care of my kid.
谢谢你！谢谢你！
Thank you. Thank you.
好了，我们去抓这个混蛋牛仔。
All right, let's go get this cowboy cocksucker.
好吧，接下来呢?
Okay, what's next?
比利·鲍尔斯的拘留听证会，法官阁下。
Detention hearing for Billy Powers, Your Honor.
他16岁。
He's 16.
没有前科。
No priors.
费用是多少?
And what's the charge?
绑架，法官阁下。
Kidnapping, Your Honor.
我们有律师吗?
Do we have a lawyer?
我们被告知他有律师，但是…好吧。这是绑架，所以没什么好谈的。
We are told he has an attorney, but... All right. It's kidnapping, so there's really nothing to talk about.
在审判日期之前，他将一直受到本法庭的监护。
He's gonna remain a ward of this court until the trial date.
我需要公设辩护律师在场，这样我们就可以正式开庭了。
I need the public defender in here, so we can make that official.
很好，法官阁下。
Very good, Your Honor.
对不起，法官阁下，我道歉。我可以吗?
I'm sorry, Your Honor, I apologize. May I?
除非你告诉我你是谁，否则你不能。
Not until you tell me who you are, you can't.
当然可以。我叫哈罗德·亨特。
Of course. My name is Harold Hunter.
我是比利·鲍尔斯的律师。
I'm representing Billy Powers here.
我再次道歉。我是新来的。
And again, I apologize. I'm new in town.
我有点迷路了。我是肯尼·沃尔什公司的。
I got a little lost. I'm with Kenny Walsh's firm.
-是吗?沃尔什先生怎么样?-他是我的英雄，所以我只会说好话。
- Oh, you are? How is Mr. Walsh? - You know, the guy's my hero, so I'm only gonna say nice things.
我刚才在跟托马斯先生说我们会继续审理这件事，在那之前你的委托人可以一直被拘留。
Well, I was just saying to Mr. Thomas here that we're gonna go ahead and set this matter for a trial, and your client can remain in custody until that time.
我不认为这是个好主意，法官阁下。
Yeah, I don't think that that's a good idea, Your Honor.
-哦，不是吗?——没有。可以吗?
- Oh, no? - No. If I may?
——请。-谢谢。
- Please. - Thank you.
在被捕时，我的当事人被发现处于酒精和大麻的影响下。
At the time of arrest, my client was found to be under the influence of alcohol and marijuana.
没有任何借口。
There's no excuse for that.
要我说，这是值得惩罚的罪名。
A charge worth punishment, if you ask me.
现在，我不是在这里谈论其他因所谓的绑架而被捕的青少年，但在我的理解中，
Now, I'm not here to speak on the other juveniles who were arrested for the so-called kidnapping, but the way I understand it,
他们违背同学的意愿，把他带回了父母的家中。
they took a classmate against his will back to one of their parents' homes.
-是的。——绑架。
- Yeah. - Kidnapping.
正确的。再说一遍，我不是来评论其他孩子做了什么，但我的当事人，他是事后出现的直到他到达现场才知道发生了什么。
Right. Again, I'm not here to speak on what those other children did, but my client, he showed up after the fact and he had no idea what was going on until after he arrived.
那他为什么不离开呢?
Well, why didn't he leave?
我不能回答这个问题，法官阁下，我并不是说这个问题不需要回答。
I can't answer that question, Your Honor, and I'm not implying that that question doesn't need to be answered.
他是个好孩子。没有前科。
He's a good kid. No priors.
我是说，除了没有做出正确的决定立即离开，当然，还有抽烟喝酒，比利·鲍尔斯唯一犯的错就是品味差。
I mean, aside from not making the right decision to leave immediately, and, of course, the drinking and smoking, the only thing Billy Powers is guilty of is bad taste.
我认为他应该被允许在候审期间和他母亲住在一起。
I believe that he should be allowed to stay with his mother while awaiting trial.
当然，有了法院的监控建议。
Of course, with the court's recommendation for monitoring.
这就引出了我的下一个问题。妈妈在哪里?
Well, that leads me to my next question. Where is the mother?
-我来了，法官阁下-她来了。
- I'm here, Your Honor. - She's here.
女士，请上来。
Ma'am, come up here, please.
我在看一份报告，女士，上面说执法部门试图给你的住处打几个电话。
I'm looking at a report, ma'am, that says that law enforcement attempted to make several calls to your residence.
这些电话都没有人接。
Those phone calls were never answered.
还有迹象表明缓刑办公室也这么做了，但没有回电吗?
There's also indication that the probation office did as well, yet no call back?
你没有试图联系任何人吗?
No attempt by you to contact anyone?
我不能在没有合理解释的情况下把你儿子交给你监护。
I cannot release your son into your custody without a reasonable explanation.
我很害怕。
I was scared.
我很害怕，不知道该怎么办。
I was so scared, I didn't know what to do.
我们只有彼此。
We only have each other.
比利的父亲死于…在2015年的一场可怕的划船事故中。
Billy's father died in a... in a horrible boating accident back in 2015.
比利只是个孩子。
Billy was just a boy.
当我收到短信时，我…我做了一些调查，得知这些指控的严重性后，我崩溃了，再也没有重新站起来的决心。
When I received the messages, I, uh... I did some research, and upon learning the severity of the charges, I just broke down and I couldn't find the will to get back up.
我就知道我们请不起律师。
I knew we couldn't afford an attorney.
我目前打三份工，只能勉强度日。
I'm currently working three jobs just so we can get by.
我不知道我是怎么做到的，但是…不知怎么的，我设法让自己振作起来，我联系了亨特先生，他告诉我比利遇到了大麻烦，
I don't know how I did it, but... somehow I managed to pick myself back up, and I reached out to Mr. Hunter here, and he told me that Billy was in a lot of trouble,
但与此同时，他不会容忍这种不公。
but at the same time, he wasn't gonna stand for this injustice.
他相信法律…而且，出于他的好心……他同意免费接手比利的案子。
He believes in the law... and, out of the goodness of his heart... he agreed to take Billy's case on free of charge.
上帝保佑你。
God bless you.
他是个好孩子，法官阁下
He's a good boy, Your Honor.
他应该得到更好的待遇。
He deserves better.
如果要怪谁，那就是我。
If there's anyone to blame here, it's me.
我只是太忙了，你知道…我一直忙于三份工作，还有癌症……是的，法官阁下，她显然很沮丧而且…我觉得我们应该搬到…
I've just been so busy, you know... I've been so busy with the three jobs - and the-- and the cancer... Yeah, uh, Your Honor, she's obviously upset and, uh... I think that we should, uh, move to...
移动，真的。
to move, really.
但你懂的，你懂的。
Um, but you get-- you get the point.
-我知道这不是你的错。-我知道，真的
- And I know it is not your fault. -  I recognize that, I do.
你母亲和她的信仰，不是使徒的，而是她自己的。
Your mother and her beliefs, they were not that of the Apostle, but of her own.
她灌输给你的，我需要你明白这一点。
She instilled them into you, and I need you to see that.
然后是钢环和铁十字。
And then the steel rings with the iron cross.
你知道铁十字架吗?当你……就像在拳击场上。这是肌肉的运动?
You know the iron cross? When you do... like this in the rings. It's the muscle moves, okay?
吊环之后，是双杠。
After rings, you got parallel bars.
那到底是谁?
Who the hell is that?
我能帮你吗?
Can I help you?
沃特·博格斯的披萨送过来了。
Yeah, we got a pizza delivery for Walter Boggs.
我们又没叫披萨。
We didn't order no fucking pizza.
总有人会把它吃掉的。
Well, somebody's gonna eat it.
我要出来了!
I'm coming out!
他妈的!
Fuck!
沃尔特!
Walter!
你混蛋!
You cocksucker!
我进来了，你个混蛋!
I'm coming in, you motherfucker!
我进来了!
I'm coming in!
沃尔特!
Walter!
出来，出来，你这个混蛋!
Come out, come out, you cocksucker!
大灰狼来收钱了。
Big bad wolf is here to collect.
快来拿!
Come and get it!
我有一整晚的时间，操!
I got all night, fuck-o!
妈的，我住这儿。
Shit, I live here.
出来吧，出来吧，沃尔特。大家一起说
Come on, come out, Walt. Let's talk.
不，你是我的客人。我坚持。
No, you're my guest. I insist.
嘿,哥们。
Hey, buddy.
嗨,爸爸。
Hey, Dad.
-很高兴见到你。——谢谢。
- It's good to see you. - Thanks.
我们该离开这里吗?
Should we get out of here?
是啊，这可能是个好主意，对吧?
Yeah, that's probably a good idea, huh?
你们要带我去我妈家吗?
You guys are gonna take me to my mom's?
这是你想要的吗?
Is that what you want?
嗯。
Uh-uh.
哥斯达黎加吗?
Costa Rica?
沃尔特!
Walter!
我告诉过你我有一整晚的时间沃尔特。
I told you I got all night... Walter.
是吗?你确定吗?
Yeah? You sure about that now?
他妈的。
Fuck.
是的,操。去你妈的。
Yeah, fuck. Fuck you.
他妈的!
Fuck!
你还好吗?
Are you okay?
——成龙!——爸爸!
- Jackie! - Dad!
爸爸!
Dad!
嘿，住手!
Hey, stop it!
你要拿那个做什么，比利?
What are you gonna do with that, Billy?
让他走吧。
Let him go.
你现在也很坚强了，比利?
You're a tough guy now too, Billy?
很多球，孩子。
A lot of balls, kid.
你想玩枪?
You want to play guns?
你他妈的想玩枪吗?
You want to play fucking guns?
不，退后。回来。回来。回来。
No, get back. Get back. Get back. Get back.
来吧。来吧。
Come on. Come on.
好样的，杰基。
Heart of a lion, Jackie.
狮子的心。
Heart of a lion.
确保我再也见不到你，好吗?
Make sure I never see you again, okay?
你不会。
You won't.
嘿,杰基。
Hey, Jackie.
你打人还是像个娘们。
You still hit like a girl.
-事情是这样的-告诉我。
- Here's what's gonna happen. - Tell me.
你要承认在餐厅里杀了那个人然后这事就结束了。
You're gonna confess to killing that guy in the diner and then this shit is over.
-我说真的。结束了。——好的。
- I mean it. Over. - Okay.
比利呢?
What about Billy?
什么……哇!
What... Whoa!
别动，好吗?
Don't fucking move, all right?
比利是个大男孩。我会给他写信的。
Billy is a big boy. I'll write to him.
你现在是持枪的硬汉了吗?
What are you, a tough guy with a gun now?
-我该怕你吗?-这不是我的错。
- I'm supposed to be scared of you? - This is not my fault.
我们陷入这种境地不是因为我。
We are not in this situation because of me.
不,不。我说的不是那个。
No, no. I'm not talking about that.
我说的是你。
I'm talking about you specifically.
一日贱，终身贱。
Once a bitch, always a bitch.
-如果我是个婊子…——嗯。
- If I'm a bitch... - Uh-huh.
．..因为每次我帮你的时候，我的屁股都会被操!
...it's because every single time I help you out, I get fucked in the ass!
你刚来中央监狱的第一天就吓得尿裤子了。
You looked like you were gonna piss yourself your first day at Central.
如果不是我，你在那里连三秒钟都坚持不了，好吗?
If it wasn't for me, you wouldn't have lasted three seconds in that place, okay?
杰基，我他妈没开玩笑，好吗?
Jackie, I'm not fucking playing, all right?
你给我照做，不然我就开枪了。
You're gonna do it, or I'm gonna fucking shoot you.
我看你敢不敢把枪放下。
I fucking dare you to put that gun down.
我他妈敢打赌。请。
I fucking dare you. Please.
-没有他妈的枪!——好的。
- Without the fucking gun! - Okay.
我能先把该死的衣服穿上吗?
Can I put my fucking clothes on first?
穿上你的衣服!我不想让你的蛋蛋在我脸上!
Put your clothes on! I don't want your balls in my face!
-哦，妈的!——操!他妈的……
- Oh, fuck! - Fuck! Fucking...
哦!
Oh!